(Sheldon:)The parade.
(Penny:)That reminds me. I usually go back
to Nebraska for Thanksgiving.
(Penny:)This year, they're calling it off
on account of my brother's trial.
(Leonard:)-What's he on trial for?
-Oh, just a big misunderstanding.
You know, you'd like my brother.
He's kind of a chemist.
(Penny:)I was thinking
I'd have Thanksgiving here.
(Penny:)-And you are all invited.
-Oh, I'll be there.
(Sheldon:)Will you be serving cranberry jelly
or cranberry sauce?
(Penny:)I guess I could serve both.
(Sheldon:)You guess? You don't seem
to have much of a handle on this.
(Howard:)Yeah, I really wish I could,
Penny, but every year...
(Howard:)...my mother has all the relatives over
and cooks up her famous tur-briska-fil.
(Penny:)Tur-briska-fil?
A turkey stuffed with a brisket
stuffed with gefilte fish.
(Howard:)It's not as good as it sounds.
(Penny:)Raj, what about you?
(Howard:)Oh, he usually comes
to my house. Right, pal?
[SOBS]
Uh, all right. This year,
you don't have to eat the tur-briska-fil.
(Howard:)I don't even chew it.
I swallow it like pills.